# PROFILE

An efficient MERN stack web developer with an intuition for both system and UI design. Adept in improvising and adapting to challenges, with a proclivity to constantly optimize using creative approaches. Very research-oriented and thorough in her methods. Would like to bring her passion to any organization that appreciates it and presents ample intellectual challenges.

# PROJECTS

#### Lint 🖪

Github 17

Fullstack ecommerce website for apparels and lifestyle products. A collaboration of 4 members - built and executed in 5 days.

#### Features:

- Login/Signup, sticky & fully functional navbar, landing page
- Dynamically generated products page
- Product detail page, toggle pictures, cart popup, cart page
- Pagination, responsiveness, filtering, admin panel

#### Areas of Responsibility:

- Led the team, delegated tasks, monitored progress, planned the workflow
- Conducted daily meets, assisted team mates
- Created the backend rest API along with proper documentation
- Built cart page, worked on responsiveness of the whole website

**Tech Stack:** ReactJS | Chakra UI | Redux | NodeJS | MongoDB | ExpressJS | Mongoose

#### Oasis 🛮

Github 🛮

Ecommerce website for multipurpose products. A collaboration of 4 members - built and executed in 5 days

# **Features:**

- Admin and user authentication, product carousels
- Sorting, filtering, pagination
- Cart, wishlist (user dynamic)
- Admin panel with all CRUD functionalities, searchbar, pagination, responsponsiveness & dark mode support

## Areas of Responsibility:

- Built admin panel, acclimated to using typescript with NextJS, redux and Chakra UI
- Assisted in acquiring data

Tech Stack: ReactJS | Chakra UI | Redux | Typescript | JSON Server

#### Rimessa 🛚

Github 🛮

Ecommerce website for luxury fashion apparels.

A solo project - built & executed in 5 days

# Features:

- Responsive, dark mode supported, theming
- Carousals, cart, filtering, sorting, pagination
- User login/register
- Query strings & routing

Tech stack: Chakra UI | ReactJS | JSON Server

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Research Intern, Spartificial**

11/2022 - present

Working on a mentored land segmentation research project.

**Intern,** Shankus Medicity (Paediatric Neuro Center)

10/2019 - 11/2019 | Mehsana, Gujarat

Conducted psychological mapping, audits & training; built protocols.

# **Madhurima Poddar** Full Stack Web Developer



™ madhurimapoddar639@gmail.com

RimRaider639 Rortfolio

in Madhurima Poddar

### EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Masai School 08/2022 - present

**Bachelors of Computer Applications,** Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham 07/2021 – present | Coimbatore

A Levels, Divine Child International School 04/2019 - 03/2021 | Ahmedabad

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

JS | TS | ReactJS | NextJS | Chakra UI HTML | CSS | DSA | Redux | Testing Github | Python | JAVA | OOP | ML | SQL Web Scraping | Digital Image Processing Computer Vision | Pandas | Numpy

### SOFT SKILLS

Research | Organization | Critical Thinking Remote Work

# ACHIEVMENTS

Certified in Astronomical Data Science, Spartificial

**Machine Learning for Physics Application,** Spartificial

**Complete Python Bootcamp,** *Udemy* 

Led the 3rd Top Team - Lunathon (Hackathon), Spartificial with ISRO

#### INTERESTS

Sketching & Painting | Programming Games Building ML/DL Models | Brain Science